coveragecentre.com 2014-06-04

# Privacy Policy - Coverage Centre

**Privacy Policy for CoverageCentre.com**

If you have any question or require any information regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us via email at info@CoverageCentre.com.

At CoverageCentre.com, we value our users and that is the reason why they are so important to us. The privacy policy document of CoverageCentre.com contains details about the information that CoverageCentre.com receives and how it is then used.

**Log Files**

Like many other websites available online, CoverageCentre.com also makes use of log files. The log files contain information including type of browsers, internet protocol (IP) addresses, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, date/time stamp and number of clicks on the website, in order to track user’s behavior on the site and gather information related to the demographics of the users. IP addresses and other related information does not have any link to information that is personally identifiable.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://CoverageCentre.com/terms-and-conditions/](http://sabbkuch.pk/terms-and-conditions/)

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://CoverageCentre.com

Lahore, Punjab 54810  
Pakistan
